1040 N. Bolton Ave. Indianapolis, IN briantoombs71@gmail.com 317.250.4083

# briantoombs

Resumé

### summary

Graphic designer with over 20 years experience ranging from production artist to art director, often in the same day. Responsible for graphics and layouts for web and print. Winner of Plan2020's Love Indy design contest. Quadrupled the output of the marketing department at Buckingham.

## experience

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER | Thompson Thrift 2019 - 2020

- Art directed and designed several internal campaigns, including the Mission: Accomplished program, as well as the annual meeting.
- Updated marketing materials for all retail properties to new brand guidelines, kept those materials accurate and up-to-date with changes in vacancies and new tenants, and maintained website content, protecting their brand and maximizing their potential to generate revenue.

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER | Buckingham Companies 2011 - 2018

- Secured the first, second, and third place positions in Plan 2020's Love Indy shirt contest. Submitted designs on behalf of Buckingham, CityWay, and myself.
- Worked closely with the Creative Marketing Director and Senior Marketing
  Manager in development of branding, promotional campaigns, marketing
  materials, and more, resulting in much growth and success for Buckingham's
  many existing properties and new developments.
- Developed several properties logos and branding, including signage, print, web, email, and social media. Updated the logo and branding of many other properties, including the Monon Living properties in Broad Ripple.

#### ART DIRECTOR | Sport Graphics 2005 - 2010

- Designed logos and event packages tickets, court floors, signage, arena dressing, etc. – for many of NCAA's top ticketed college championships, including Men's and Women's Final Four.
- Created logo and logo system for WFYI, one of the nation's top PBS broadcasters.
- In addition to providing creative leadership, designed print, signage, tradeshow sets, web materials, e-mail, and multimedia. Produced a variety of materials for the Indianapolis Colts, Indiana Pacers/Fever, WFYI, Indiana University, Purdue University, USA Diving, non-profits MyFarm SF and There Is Enough, and many others.

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER | Corporate Creations, Inc. 2000 – 2005

- As an integral part of the Creative Services team, designed materials ranging from web and multi-media to print and set design.
- In an environment that was, at times, high-stress with rigid deadlines and tight budgets, served as art director and client contact for many accounts. Created successful solutions for Lawler, Delta Faucet, Home Depot, Simon Property Group, CIVC Partners, LLC, St. Vincent Hospitals, Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra, MASCO, Christian Church (Disciples of Christ), and many others.

1040 N. Bolton Ave. Indianapolis, IN briantoombs71@gmail.com 317.250.4083

# briantoombs

Resumé

### software

Adobe Creative Suite CC (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Acrobat, XD), Microsoft Office (Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Outlook)

## expertise

Emphasis on Print, with Web, Video and Multimedia design experience as well. Strong icon/logo development skills, illustration (including digital), photo manipulation, online content management systems, and fluent in various page layout programs.

### education

Bachelor of Arts Commercial/Fine Art (Double Major) Saint Francis College, Fort Wayne, IN (University of Saint Francis) GPA – 3.79

### references

Nicole Crosby, Director of Marketing and Professional Development The Garrett Companies 6363 W. Clearview Drive McCordsville, IN 46055 317-887-0142

Rob Sperka, Product Marketing Manager Project Lead The Way 5940 Gladden Dr. Indianapolis, IN 46220 317-544-8620

Lori Culp Bolin, President and Owner, Perceptual Learning Chief Strategy Officer, BrewLogix 4126 Bending Lane Greenwood, IN 46143 317-694-8714

PDF portfolio can be downloaded here:

https://www.dropbox.com/s/ugcr3rzu6q0kx4h/BT\_Portfolio20\_final.pdf?dl=0